intervalsonline.com 2018-12-26

# Intervals Privacy Policy

Pelago Corporation ("Pelago" or "We") respects the privacy of anyone who uses the Myintervals.com web site (the "Site"), and the Intervals Time, Task and Project Management Application (collectively together with any service or hosted application offered or operated by Pelago, "Intervals"), and takes your privacy concerns seriously. We have created this Privacy Policy to explain how we gather and use information about you. By using either this web site, or Intervals, you consent and agree to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. These changes will be effective when posted on the Myintervals.com web site. It is your responsibility to review our Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it. Your continued use of either this Site, or Intervals following the posting of any such change, shall constitute your acceptance thereof. We will notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy by making those changes on this Privacy Policy, and revising the date in the Last Update paragraph below.

## Collected Information: Registration/Billing/Financial

We require people who register to use Intervals to give us contact and account information, such as your name, company name, address, email address, phone number and fax number, as well as financial and billing information, such as billing name and address and credit card number.

Pelago does not distribute or share customer email addresses, except as noted in Pelago's Terms of Service, as may be required by law, for billing and collection purposes, or with Pelago customers with which such email address is, or appears to be affiliated.

As you interact with our Site and Intervals, we automatically collect information from your browser or device, which may include your IP address, device identification, browser type, internet service provider, geolocation data, the referring or exit pages, the page you requested, and Cookie information. We log all access to Intervals by IP address, so we can verify that no unauthorized access has happened while the logs are kept. 

Pelago uses the information that we collect to set up Intervals for individuals and their organizations. We may also use the information to contact customers and prospects to discuss their interest in our company, Intervals or service we provide and ways to improve Intervals, and to send information regarding our company or partners, including information on promotions and events. We may also email a company newsletter and updates about Intervals or Pelago. You can opt out of receiving these communications by replying to them at the time they are distributed or at any time by emailing support@myintervals.com.

All financial and billing information that we collect through the Myintervals.com web site and through an Intervals is used solely to bill for Intervals or check the qualifications of prospective customers. Pelago does not use this billing information for marketing or promotional purposes. Pelago uses third part(ies) to manage credit card processing. Except as provided for in Pelago's Terms of Service, Pelago does not disclose this information to any third parties not involved in billing or collecting fees due for Intervals or its use.

## Hosted Data

Customers of the Service will be using the Site and Intervals to host data and information ("Customer Data"). Pelago will not review, share, distribute, print or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the Terms of Service, as may be required by law or pursuant to the direction of the Customer. Individual records may at times be viewed or accessed for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issue, or suspected violation of the Terms of Service or as may be required by law. Of course, customers of Intervals are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and passwords.

## Aggregate Data

Pelago may also collect certain information from visitors to and customers of Myintervals.com or Intervals, such as Internet addresses. This information is used to help us better manage Intervals, diagnose technical problems, administer the Site and Service, find improvements, and provide a higher level of customer service. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers, including profile information, account data and browser type, which information may be shared with third parties.

## Cookies

When you come to the Site, or use Intervals, a cookie will be sent to your computer. Cookies are files stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive when you visit a website. Cookies are used to help us authenticate you, provide timesaving shortcuts and preferences and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. There are both session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. They include such information as a unique identifier for your browser. Pelago uses session cookies to allow Intervals and the Site to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows us to process your online transactions and requests. Pelago uses persistent cookies to identify the fact that you are a customer of Intervals or prior visitor to the Site, as well as to save and retrieve other per-customer device preferences. Customers and visitors who disable their Web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Site, but may have difficulties accessing or using Intervals.

Third Party Cookies: We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our Site to help us administer our Site and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual website visitors to any personally identifiable information.

## Correcting And Updating Your Information

If you wish to update, correct, or delete any personal information we have collected, you may do so by updating the My Account section found in the Intervals online application. You can also correct, update, or delete personal information by emailing support@myintervals.com.

## Children

The Site and Intervals are intended solely for persons 13 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 13 you may not access or use them. By using the Site or Intervals, you represent and warrant to us that you are 13 years of age or older.

## No Error-Free Performance/Limitation Of Liability

We do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. We welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have. PELAGO WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INJURY, HARM OR DAMAGES, INCLUDING INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, RELATING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THE PERFORMANCE THEREOF, OR THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED THEREIN, WHETHER BY ITSELF OR ANY THIRD PARTY, IN EXCESS OF ANY AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID PELAGO FOR YOUR USE OF INTERVALS.

## Disclosures Required by Law

We reserve the right to disclose any information collected by Pelago, including your personally identifiable information, if required to do so by law or pursuant to a request by the government or law enforcement.

## Mergers and Acquisitions

Anything in this Privacy Policy notwithstanding, in the event that Pelago or a portion of its assets are acquired by or sold to another company, any of the information collected by Pelago and/or described in this Privacy Policy, including customer and personally identifiable information, may be among the transferred assets.

## Use of Contractors

We may retain the use of outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (for example, to help provide technical support services, deliver new products or services, or bill and collect). At times, we may disclose relevant personally identifiable information about you to our contractors so they may provide these specific services for us.

## Links to Third Party Web Sites

Our site may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software, do not review their privacy practices or policies, and make no representations concerning the privacy of any information you enter outside of the Site.

## Public Forums

This Site and Intervals make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or newsgroups available to its visitors, and users of Intervals. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose information, including personally identifiable information, there.

## Opt-Out Policy

Pelago offers you a means to choose how we may use information you provided. If, at any time after registering for or ordering Intervals, you change your mind about receiving promotional information from us or about sharing information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Send your request to support@myintervals.com.

## Contact Information

Questions, concerns, or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Pelago.

Privacy Officer  
Pelago  
412 East Haley Street, Studio #5  
Santa Barbara, CA 93101  

## Last Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25, 2018, and became effective on the same date.

» Top of page
